(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T13:41:46.576046",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
淡々言葉を吐いた
Spitting out words monotonously,
あんな思い出に泣いたのは
crying over such memories—
今日で終わりにしたくないか
don't you want to end it today?
1,2の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal,
ユーエールミー手を取り合ったのは
you and me holding hands was
僕の勇気ある行動 フェーズ
my courageous action, phase.
立ち止まらないでいいんだからね
Because it's fine not to stop here,
空々しいな この人生
how hollow this life is.
できないなんて言わないでね 言わないでね
Don't say you can't do it, don't say it.
今更なんて言わないでね
Don't say it's too late now.
僕ら今さっさと輪になって
We're finally coming together now,
回り始める
and starting to spin around.
段々嫌になって でも好きになるねえねえ
Gradually hating it, but ending up loving it.
わかんないや 自問自答も
I don't get it, I don't get it at all!
どんどん中に寄って でも離れてく
Drawing closer and drifting apart,
ポップポップ飛び乗って
oppppop jumping right in,
踊り始める
and starting to dance!
段々嫌になって でも好きになるねえねえ
Gradually hating it, but ending up loving it.
わかんないや この先もずっと
I don't get it, I don't get it at all,
僕の心を シェイクシェイク iei
shaking, shaking up our hearts, yeah!
大世界なんてないのさ
There's no such thing as a grand world,
会いたいときに会えば
if you look for it when you want to meet,
凡夫たちには 終わりですか
will it be over for us mortals?
1,2の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal,
ユーエールミー 手が触れ合ったのは
you and me touching hands was
僕の勇気ある行動 フェーズ
my courageous action, phase.
怯まったって 意味ないんだって
Being timid meant nothing,
恥ずかしがった 夢にバイバイです
saying goodbye to those shy dreams.
この先もずっとよろしくね よろしくね
Wishing you well from now on.
君と今さっさと交わって 目を逸らし合う
Crossing paths with you now,
段々嫌になって でも好きになるねえねえ
Gradually hating it, but ending up loving it.
わかんないや 自問自答も
I don't get it, I don't get it at all.
どんどん様になって 崩れ落ちてく
Falling apart into pieces,
ぱっぱっ 触れる前に 消えてしまうのは
disappearing before we can touch,
段々嫌になって でも好きになるねえねえ
Gradually hating it, but ending up loving it.
わかんないや この先もずっと
I don't get it, I don't get it at all,
分かり合えるまで bokutachi wa
until we can truly understand each other.
今更なんて言わないでね
Don't say it's too late now.
僕ら今さっさと輪になって
We're finally coming together now,
回り始める
and starting to spin around.
段々嫌になって でも好きになるねえねえ
Gradually hating it, but ending up loving it.
わかんないや 自問自答も
I don't get it, I don't get it at all!
どんどん中に寄って でも離れてく
Drawing closer and drifting apart,
ポップポップ飛び乗って
oppppop jumping right in,
踊り始める
and starting to dance!
段々嫌になって でも好きになるねえねえ
Gradually hating it, but ending up loving it.
わかんないや この先もずっと
I don't get it, I don't get it at all,
僕の心を シェイクシェイク iei
shaking, shaking up our hearts, yeah!
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god, did you see us? We're so cute!
All four of us are so cute together!
Now this is what I call a concert!
This is where the money's at! It the money's in the concert!
This is where the money's at! It—the money's in the concert!
We should do more concerts, more music... There was a concert that was coming up...
Ah, if only... if only there were tickets available right now for our concert...
Wait, what if we invite even more people?
But if we invite more people, it won't be a concert anymore, because when there's more people, they start fighting.
Oh.
You mean drama?
Drama! Wait, that's just... whenever there's too many girls in a room, drama happens.
When it does sell... Sometimes seeing girls fight...
Sometimes there's just too many girls, you know?
And, yeah.
And sometimes they just can't get along.
Mhm. But that makes for good television.
Let's content farm them.
All right, god girls, if you want to hang out with us, you have to step up your bag game.
Like, where do you even get your bag from? It looks... You don't even recognize the bag I carried today!
Oh, you... Next time, we're gonna have to take you to Bonnell.
Bonnell? Yeah.
I own that company.
You own Bonnell?
I own the sister branch of Bonnell.
Oh, my god! What are you cooking?
Oh, it's my newest recipe. It's a zero-calorie...
Oh, my god! What the-
Oh, my god! What the—
What happened?
Are you going to pick that up?
Don't tell me what to do.
You literally threw it on the ground.
No, I didn't.
You literally did it. You can't accidentally throw something on the ground.
No, I didn't. You put it there.
I put it there?
You put your ass in my stupid kitchen, you-
You put your ass in my stupid kitchen, you—
You absolute-! I did not do that!
You absolute—! I did not do that!
You literally do that! You always make shit up!
I want- did you do that?
I want— did you do that?
Did you see her do that?
Did you see that?
She literally threw a frying pan!
I saw you, Celine!
No, no, excuse me!
Yeah, so I was making this totally delicious, zero-calorie option dinner for everyone...
because I know that everyone needs to lose a little weight for the party tomorrow, and I just can't believe that she would do such a thing! Have you seen Celine? She's a total fucking-
because I know that everyone needs to lose a little weight for the party tomorrow, and I just can't believe that she would do such a thing! Have you seen Celine? She's a total fucking—
That food is going to be nasty, and you know it.
She's always on these like health strips, but it doesn't do anything for our figure!
Come, come here!
Don't tell me what to do!
Come here! You're not my mom!
Look! Look at it!
You threw that on the ground!
I've never seen that in my entire life!
You've never seen that in your entire life?
You got this for me for Christmas! I would never get you something for Christmas!
What? You got it for me for Christmas!
No, I don't want you talking about-
No, I don't want you talking about—
You got it for me for Christmas!
No, I don't want you talking about-
No, I don't want you talking about—
You always do this! Someone hold me back! Hold me back! Hold me back!
Irene, leave my friend alone! It's okay, it's okay, don't cry!
You're going to ruin your mascara, Gina!
Oh, you're always so dramatic! So dramatic!
How dare you betray me!
And she's crazy! She's crazy!
Shut the fuck up! Who even are you?
I don't even know why the fuck I'm here!
I was just trying-
I was just trying—
I was just here to like promote my music and like all these, you know, really rich girls here.
I'm so honored to be here, honestly, but I don't know what the fuck went on.
Like, what the fuck? I think it's the water. There's something in the water.
I don't even know why Irene was here.
Who invited her?
She's sexy.
Why are you always so dramatic?
Me dramatic?
Why do you always make shit up?
You live by the drama! You are fake!
The only thing about me that's fake is my tits.
You...
Yeah, her tits are fake.
I would know, I paid for them.
Well, I was really insecure about my chest, so you know, I got it, yep, you know, daddy paid for...
No! Wait, was it China? Oh my god, I forgot about that. I owe her, she's the best.
It's a flight.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay. I'm literally not okay.
Did you see what she did to me?
I saw.
That was unbelievable! Our food, and I was looking forward to that! I was a new low-calorie option!
Excuse me, like, you should stop acting like that, you know, how old are you?
Excuse me?
I want to talk to her manager! You're literally a kid!
What? Oh my god, shut up!
Bijou always has my back, girl.
I know she'll throw down with me.
Bijou, are you getting my good side? Make sure you get the right angle. This is for TV, right? Yeah, take me out.
Anyway, Celine is a... I don't know what kind of prompt she has with my girl, Gina.
But if she continues with this, we're going to have to throw hands. She better catch me outside, how about that, if you know what I mean. I think she needs a wakeup call.
Bijou is such a follower. She doesn't have a single thought in that empty head of hers. If you would take her head and rattle it, it would sound like a baby rattle.
You guys are so loud. We're going to get a noise complaint, and it's going to be so embarrassing for you because...
The only noise complaint we'll get is when you're in your bedroom.
My bedroom?
What is- What does that mean? A bedroom?
Well, at least this apartment isn't under my name, so you are going to get in trouble.
I will send you to jail, my daddy's a lawyer.
You know what? My daddy owns your daddy.
Might be under your daddy, but...
He's a lawyer. I think your daddy's under my daddy.
In- in- more ways than one.
Do you see what she's doing to me, Bijou? I saw, girl.
Oh, so you have a problem with German and ISIS?
Too many boots! Too many boots!
She cursed me! She cursed me! Did you guys see that? She cursed me! She cursed me!
She did nothing! She did nothing! She blessed me!
Rachel threw herself on the floor. I saw it happen. She's just so dramatic.
She cursed me! She cursed me! Did you guys see that? She cursed me! She cursed me! She cursed me!
Wait, she's such a pick-me girl. That Rachel, what a pick-me. Kind of a bitch.
I pick her, though. Have you seen her thunder thighs? Dang, I want to- I want to bite that. Don't tell her, though. Cut that out! Cut that out!
Che cazzo... Stai parlando di quella... Se mi tocca di nuovo, io non sara faccio più. Basta! Ho finito.
What the fuck... You're talking about that... If she touches me again, I'm not doing this anymore. Enough! I'm done.
Rachel is so sweet. She always got my back. Sometimes she falls down though, but you know, it helps for my cause, so it's okay.
You, you are a problem, and you are a danger to society!
Danger to society? You're a danger to society!
I mean, come on, join us, join us. Don't start touching each other. This is getting a little too far, I think.
I got you, girl! I got you! Get up! Get up! Now you're ruining your outfit!
Anyway, guys, I'm kind of hungry. Do you want... I was making a new low-calorie recipe that I... cuz you really need to slim down.
If you are cooking, I guess everyone's going to lose their appetite.
I thought Gina was trained by a Michelin chef. I was. No, she's just lying. She always makes up the shit. Namaste.
Namaste. Namaste. Oh, I can expect something so nutritious. It's really nutritious.
How dare you try to ruin our perfect five-star meal?
We were so looking forward to it.
Five stars, you ruined Thanksgiving!
And you are no one to tell her what to do!
Well, I can say whatever...
Hey, Rachel, leave Visual alone.
Hey, leave Visual alone.
So what are we here for anyways?
Dinner!
Dinner! Dinner!
Do we get to actually eat?
Yeah!
How we going to eat? That's right.
Are we going to eat?
Are we going to eat? Oh my god!
Eat.
Anyways, I want to go back to the kitchen and I'm going to finish cooking.
Yeah, where you belong?
You little-
Hold on, you have to hold me back off of her!
Oh, you'd better hold me back!
Animal abuse!
Hold it back up! Animal abuse!
Are you okay, girl?
Girl, are you okay?
Animal abuse!
Animal abuse here!
Just because your dad is a lawyer...
doesn't mean you can do whatever you want!
The fork's not suit you!
Make me look good in the edit, okay?
Check them out.
I feel like that was too many swear words.
And they said, "True, there's too many beepings in there."
Yeah, it was almost like a more Skel-...
Or censored fuck?
Or shit!
I just, I don't know.
I would never swear on your channel, by the way.
Yeah, you're so sweet.
That's really nice of you. I feel like...
I would never fucking do that, that's so messed up of someone to do.
Yeah, I just... Really fucked up.
I just wish they would have edited that out, you know?
Yeah, I just... I'm really uncomfortable right now.
I'm only...
Five minutes old, I'm not allowed to hear those words.
I'm just really scared.
It's also just... I don't think we're going to make any money out of that because it's not going to be allowed to be aired.
They're going to demonetize our channel!
What if? What if we have a show, but instead of like real people, it's scripted?
Oh, and then we can make sure that there's no curse words in it and we'll take them all out.
Yeah, yeah.
It can still be drama, right?
Mm. But just no...
No cursing, please. Please no cursing on our channel.
PREVIOUSLY ON: HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH - THE TALE OF BEAVER AND THINKER.
TWO UNLIKELY SURVIVORS FIND EACH OTHER IN THE MIDDLE OF THE APOCALYPSE, AND ALTHOUGH WARY, THEY'VE COME TO FIND COMFORT IN EACH OTHER'S PRESENCE.
HAUNTED BY THEIR PAST, AFRAID OF A FUTURE THAT MAY NEVER COME, WILL THEY EVER BE ABLE TO OVERCOME THEIR STRUGGLES AND REACH MUTUAL UNDERSTANDING IN A DYING WORLD? FOR MORE INFORMATION, PLEASE WATCH SEASON 1 AIRED ON JULY
So have you thought about it?
You just, you just always say things, but in reality, I love you.
No, you love your wife!
She's dead now.
You don't even remember.
You, what are you even? I'm the beaver.
Oh man, if I was a beaver, I'd be eating so good right now.
Is that because I have wood? Look at my wood! Check it out!
Are you impressed with my wood?
So you are love for nothing.
I can provide for you.
You love your wife! You don't understand!
But still love your wife!
The past seven days that we've learned to survive.
You just want me for my body!
You're not interested in my mind!
I want you for your mind and the thinker!
I want you. No. No. No, you have to understand.
You're wrong! No, please!
You don't have to feel like this! Look at my wood!
No, I don't want to look at your wood!
Look at my wood! Look at my wood!
I don't want your wood!
But you'll be so full!
No, ew! Ew!
Put that away! Look at my wood! You don't even want it for your mind!
You want me for-
A skeleton! Run away! Run away!
I'll protect us!
I mean, I mean, Beaver!
I'm the beaver! I'm not CG, I'm a beaver! I'm the beaver!
Beaver, be careful! I...
Oh my god, where'd you get that weapon? I've never seen you use that before.
Yeah, I I I bought it from the one pawn shop owner, remember?
Oh yeah!
The guy with the one eye? Was it the one eye?
No.
Watch out! Watch out! I'm so skilled!
I'm so skilled! So cool!
Oh my god, this skeleton, she's so cool!
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
Someday, the light of love in your eyes
時を超えて
will transcend time,
滅び急ぐ
rushing toward ruin,
世界の夢を 確実に一つ壊すだろう
destroying one dream of the world for sure.
躊躇いを飲み干して
Swallow down your hesitation.
君が望むものは何? こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
What is it that you wish for? Where does this greedy yearning lead?
微かな明日はあるの?
Is there a faint tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
Like the ancient magic
古の魔法のように 闇さえ砕く力で
I dreamed of as a child, with power to crush even the darkness
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to meet your smiling face.
怯えるこの手の中には 手折られた花の勇気
In these trembling hands is the courage of plucked flowers.
想いだけが頼る全て 光を呼び覚ます願い
Feelings are all I rely on, a wish that awakens the light.
いつか君も誰かの為に 強い力を望むのだろう
Someday, you too will desire great power for someone's sake.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に 未知の言葉が生まれて来る
In the night when love gripped my heart, unknown words are born.
迷わずに行けるなら 心が砕けてもいいわ
If I can go on without hesitation, I don't mind if my heart shatters.
いつも目の前の哀しみに 立ち向かう為の呪文が欲しい
I want a spell to face the sorrow right before my eyes.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are a memory still dreaming,
私は眠らない明日
I am the sleepless tomorrow.
二人が出会う奇跡を 勝ち取る為に進むわ
I will press forward to win the miracle of our meeting.
怯えるこの手の中には 手折られた花の刃
In these trembling hands is a blade of plucked flowers.
想いだけが生きる全て 心に振りかざす願い
Feelings alone are all I live for, a wish I brandish in my heart.
囚われた太陽の輝く 不思議の国が好きだった頃
When I loved the wonderland illuminated by captive suns,
願いはきっと叶うと 教えるお伽噺を信じた
I believed the fairy tales that taught wishes would come true.
静かに咲き乱れていた 古の魔法優しい
Gently blooming in silence, ancient magic whispered softly.
囚われた太陽の輝く 不思議の国が好きだった頃
When I loved the wonderland illuminated by captive suns,
願いはきっと叶うと 教えるお伽噺を信じた
I believed the fairy tales that taught wishes would come true.
涙はきっと叶うと 教えるお伽噺を信じた
I believed the fairy tales that taught tears would come true.
静かに咲き乱れていた 古の魔法優しく
Gently blooming in silence, ancient magic whispered softly.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Blooming in silence,
古の魔法優しい
ancient magic softly...
世界を変える力が
The power to change the world
その手にあると囁く
whispers that it lies in your hands.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let us have an unending dream
君と行く時の中で
during this time I go through with you.
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all I live for,
命を作るのは願い
what creates life is this wish.
They brought them back to kill them off?
They killed a main character like, not - not it's not a big cast! It's literally just two characters.
They killed a main character like—not, it's not a big cast! It's literally just two characters.
I can't believe that you would have a finale of a show years ago, and then you would do a reunion episode to kill the main character!
I can't believe you'd have a show's finale years ago, and then do a reunion episode to kill the main characters!
They're so still!
Oh my god... Well,
These writers don't know what they're doing! That's not going to make any...
We should trash this idea! This is a terrible idea.
You know what? Not my canon.
Not my canon!
This is not my show!
No, no. This is just a cash grab. I hate it.
Okay, okay.
You know what else is a cash grab?
What? What?
The Autofister Merchandiiise!
The Autofister merchandise!
If only we could have someone here that can tell us about it. Oh!
If only we could have someone here who can tell us about it. Oh!
mina-san, hey everyone, it's me, Mori Calliope from Hololive English Myth, coming here to you today, to ask you to please purchase this merchandise...
The Autofister Net Merch set! Ever wanted a Gremtomo keychain...
...or uh, Gimimi or Cemimi?
Or better yet, an acrylic stand with Autofister on it!
(noise of enthusiasm) for the low low price 99.99 [price will be beeped] this can be yours!
For the low, low price of 99.99 [price will be beeped], this can be yours!
Oh... Oh wow!
For the low low price 99.99 open bracket price will be beeped close bracket...
For the low, low price of 99.99 [price will be beeped]...
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry... Um...
This, this can be yours! This can be yours!
And if you purchase now!! double exclamation point I will say this one super awesome word out loud! [pregnant silence] league of legends...
And if you purchase now!! I will say this one super awesome word out loud! League of Legends...
That's uh... that's two words. Wait, no I, okay, I see, I see what's under... that's... that's three words. I'm not saying that.
That's uh... that's two words. Wait, no—okay, I see what's under... That's three words. I'm not saying that.
Mori, did you check the script beforehand?
Ooooh! This was a bad idea! This is a freaking bad idea! I don't know why I agreed to this! Ooooh!
Hololive Legends, thank you. And buy the merchandise.
Oh wow, thanks Calli!
She loves that. She loves our merch.
(Grow up! Nah mean?)
(Track Giga)
劣等上等 BRING IT ON
Bottom to top, BRING IT ON
列島上々 不眠日本
Japan's awake, sleepless nation
子供騙しのマゼマテリカ
Childish magic mathematica
バレてんだってそんなのってプライドがないや
Found out, but we've got no pride left
ごり派閥 警鐘 気取りで 高みの見物ばかりじゃつまんないね (It's boring)
Acting high and mighty, watching from above is so boring (It's boring)
ほらもっと 間違って上等
Come on, make mistakes, bring it on
退屈に手をかけて
Reaching out to boredom
ママ、やっぱあたしは
Mama, I know I can't end up
こんなところじゃ終われない
In a place like this!
ぬるくて気が触れそう
It's so lukewarm I'm going crazy
ごっこ遊びも芝居もさようなら
Goodbye to make-believe and acting
ずっとこのままなんてさ いらないよ
I don't want to stay like this forever!
ダッダッダ あたし大人になる
Da-da-da, I'm growing up
酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Tasting all the sweet and sour things
パッパッパ 変わる時代
Pa-pa-pa, the times are changing
悪いことばかりじゃないでしょ
It can't all be bad, right?
過去も、罪も、罰も、すべて
All the past, sins, and punishments
素手で、愛で 生き抜いてやり返すわ
Surviving it all barehanded with love
yeah, 挑発 あたし達はno doubt
Yeah, provocation, we are no doubt
緑のアイツにばっか構ってんじぇ
Always fussing over that green one
さあburn up いつになったら貰える合格
Now burn up, when will we get our passing grade?
赤ペンイレテヨ どこがダメなんですか
Red pen it, what's wrong with it anyway?
酒女金ドラッグ ヤチヤッテコンプラ
Booze, women, money, drugs, compliance drama
チルってaiight… 冗談じゃんブラックジョーク
Chill out, aight... Just a black joke
中指立てたくなるような事情
Situations that make you want to flip the bird
ありすぎて手が足りねえからhands up
There are too many, can't keep up, so hands up
and what's up 最低? もともとだろ bring it on
And what's up, lowest? Bring it on from the start
「まあまあ」なんか要らない 欲しがります死ぬまでは
We don't need 'calm down', we'll want it till we die
伸ばした背中 育った街に投げキス
Stretched-out back, blowing a kiss to our hometown
見場はこっから 覚悟しときな
The real show starts here, better brace yourselves
ダッダッダ ぼくらは大人になる
Da-da-da, we're growing up
カウンター狙い 最低な日々に
Aiming for a counter in these lowest days
(Grow up! Nah mean?)
(Track Giga)
劣等上等 BRING IT ON
Lower one's life, BRING IT ON
列島上々 不眠日本
Archipelagic high, sleepless Japan
子供騙しのマゼマテリカ
Mathematica that only fools children
ご立派 警鐘 気取ってさ
Putting on airs of righteous alarms
高みの見物ばかりじゃつまんない
Just watching from high above is so boring
ほらもっと 間違って上等
Come on, make mistakes, that's even better
退屈に手をかけて
Take hold of the boredom
こんなところじゃ終われない
There's no way I'm ending up in a place like this
ぬくぬく 気触れそうぜ
It's so lukewarm I feel like I'm losing my mind
ごっこ遊びも芝居もさようなら
Goodbye to playing house, goodbye to acting
ダッタッタ 大人になる
Da-da-da, I am becoming an adult
酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Now tasting both the sweet and the sour
Let's go!
パパパッ 変わる時代
Pa-pa-pa, the changing times
悪いことばかりじゃないでしょ
It's not all going to be bad, is it?
過去も、罪も、罰も、すべて
The past, the sins, the punishments, everything
素手で、愛で、
With bare hands, with love
生き抜いてやり返すわ
I'll survive and strike back
yeah, 挑発
yeah, provocation
あたし達はno doubt
we have no doubt
緑のアイツにばっか構ってんね
You're only paying attention to that green one over there
さあburn up
Now burn up
いつになったら貰える合格
When will I ever get a passing grade?
赤ペンいれてよ どこがダメなんですか
Put your red pen to it, where am I going wrong?
酒女金ドラッグコンプライアンス
Alcohol, women, money, drugs, compliance
チルってaiight... 冗談じゃんブラックジョーク
Chilling is a-alright... just kidding, it's a black joke
中指立てたくなるような事情 ありすぎて指足りねえからhands up and what's up
Reasons that make you want to put up your middle finger, there are too many, my fingers aren't enough, so hands up and what's up
最低? もともとだろ bring it on
Lowest? It was like that from the start, bring it on
「まあまあ」なんかいらない 欲しがります死ぬまでは
I don't need any "so-so" stuff, I'll keep wanting until the day I die
伸びた背中 育んだ街に投げキス
Height grown tall, blowing a kiss to the town I grew up in
見せ場はこっから 覚悟しとけよ
This is where the highlight begins, better be prepared
ダッタッタ 僕ら大人になる
Da-da-da, we are becoming an adult
カウンター狙い 最低な日々に
Aiming for a counter-attack on these miserable days
粛々とかます一撃
Calmly delivering a single blow
誰も読めない先まだあいこでしょ
The future is still unreadable, it's still a tie, right?
バグも、ロスも、ズレも、すべて
Bugs, losses, discrepancies, everything
素手で、生きて! 生き抜いて覆すよ
With bare hands, live! Survive and overturn it
くだらないことばかりが譲れない
There's only nonsense I can't back down on
わかるか?あたしの美学
Do you understand? My aesthetic
この馬鹿正直な拳ひとつが 切り札
This single, honest-to-a-fault fist of mine is my trump card
がなる劣等 一抜けろさらば!
The roaring inferiority, drop out and farewell!
ダッタッタ あたし大人になる
Da-da-da, I am becoming an adult
酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Now tasting both the sweet and the sour
爛々 交わるミライ
Brightly intersecting futures
もう子供じゃないのわかるでしょ
You know we aren't children anymore, right?
時代 機会 待ってくれない
Times and opportunities won't wait for you
素手で、捨て身で、生き抜いて上等だわ
With bare hands, with a desperate resolve, surviving is what's best
愛ある時代
An era with love
それでは皆様 お先に bye, guys!
Well then, everyone, bye guys!
Are you thinking?
What I'm thinking?
I think I am!
Oh my god.
We have to bring this.
Write this down!
Write this down right now! Put on the suit!
Yeah!
Oh my god, they're going to love this.
They're going to love it.
They're going to love us.
They love us.
This is part.
This is cancelled.
I'm going to give up on my dreams.
Never give up on your dreams.
Really?
Yeah, I feel like
You had half a good idea.
And you had half a good idea too.
And together,
that's a whole good idea.
We'll get the funding one day.
So thank you very much everyone that helped us work on all these shows together. Um, thank you to all our beautiful, wonderful guests and thank you to you, Grams and Otomos, Grams at home, at home watching us, watching us today, today during our TV show.
Um, please sign our petition,
look at the credits, and look at the credits. And,
don't don't don't forget there is something else coming up in just minutes.
What right after this, so don't change the channel.
Don't change the channel just yet. Put down that remote.
Put it down.
Yes, gun to your head, put it down right now.
Put down the remote right now, there's something really really cool coming up right after this!
Yay!